Arts and Sciences, College of; Records ua600
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1955-1995; 2; 18.4 cubic ft.
  - Humanities Building, 1966-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - East Podium, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - West Podium, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Western Extension Podium, 1968-1970; 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Space hedset Problems, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Special Space Needs for Administration, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Space Planning, 1967; 1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Search Committee for Dean of Humanities, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cinema Major, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Classics, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Funds, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Institutional Funds, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Comparative and World Literature, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Deans Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Department Chairman, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Department Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Department Reviews Humanities, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Dept Statistics, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Degrees Awarded, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Assistantships, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Division of Humanities Memoranda, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Assistantships, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Fellowships, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Division of Humanities Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Division of Humanities Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Division of Humanities Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Division of Humanities Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Departmental Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Humm Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Division of Humanities Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment, Spring (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Enrollment, Fall (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Figures, Fall (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Enrollment, Fall/Spring (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Enrollment, fall (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Enrollment Figures, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Budget Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Transfer, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Records from Notebook, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Old Faculty Roster, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Lines, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Lines, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Term Practice, 1975 October 15; 1975 June 6 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Rosters, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Line, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Line, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Summer Session Planning, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Art and Music, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Classics, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Comparative Literature, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - English, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - German- Slav, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - German Slav, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Philosophy, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Romance Languages, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Speech and Dramatic Art, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Student Advising, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Art, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Art Problems, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Asian Languages And Cultures, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - University of the Air, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Summer Sessions, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - South Asian Program, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Short Courses, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Salaries, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Publications File, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Recruitment Meetings, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Philosophy, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Potsdam, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Neglected Languages Program, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Petersons Guides, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Madrid Program, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Major Activities, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Linguistics Program, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Long Range Planning, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Hebrew, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Kattering Project, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Linguistics, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Foreign Language Requirements, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Fellowships Request, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Faculty Lists, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - East European Studies, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Conversations in Disciplines, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Departmental Annual Report Data, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Continuing Appointments, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - College Committees and Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Supplies, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - S.A, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Albert Schweitzer Chair, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - British Teachers, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Slavic, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Speech and Dramatic Art, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Program in Agenda Speech, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Summer School, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Teaching Loads, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Workload Analysis, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ADA Craig Walker Award Female Graduate, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Division Meetings, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Minutes Divisional Meetings, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Division Meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Humanities and Fine Arts College, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - English Courses, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Courses Art, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Enrollment, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Slavic ID Courses, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Untitled, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Untitled, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Untitled, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Untitled, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Untitled, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Untitled, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts Annual Reports, 1970-1971; 1972-1973; 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - CWL, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts Annual Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Humanities Council, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Humanistic Studies, 1973-1979; 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Division of Humanities Summer Sessions, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Summer Sessions, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Summer School Planning, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Summer School Planning, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Humanities Chairmen, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rhetoric and Public Address, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dean + Assoc Dean Searches, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - English, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - English Search Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - R.P.A Search Com, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - For Dean Perlmutter- Report of Department Chairmanship Romance Lang, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - V.P Candidates, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Temp Services and Allocations, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Temp Service Allocations, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Philosophy, 1963; 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Proposed Radin Television, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Registration, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Research Fellowships, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Rhetoric and Public Address, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Rom. Language, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Chairmanship Romance Lang, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Assistants and Fellows, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Assistantships and Fellowships, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - N.D.E.A. Fellowships, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Promotions and Continuing Appointments, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Hebrew Language Courses, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Humanities, 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - International Studies Executive Assistant, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Judaic Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Minutes = Meeting of Joint Committee on Procedures, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Language Lab., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Latin American, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Misc, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Music, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - National Endowment for the humanities, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Allocation of Positions, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - College Personnel Data, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Humanities Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Continuing Appointments, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Humanities Faculty Changes, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - General Information are Term Appointments, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Appointment Problems, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - New Appointment, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - English Teachers from France and Belgium, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Enrollment, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Humanities Enrollments, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Forum, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Forum, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Equipment, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Humanities Budgets, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Request For Supplementary Funds, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - IBM Sheets Faculty Salaries, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Doctor of Arts Degree, 1973 January (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Staff Concerns, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Humanities Division Chairmens Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Humanities Division Chairmens Meetings, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Humanities Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Humanities Committee for Academic Development, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Students, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Proposal, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - New Graduate Courses, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Degree Program Initiation Dates, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Degree Flaws, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - German and Slavic Languages, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Search Committee Report, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - General File, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Development Plan for Econ., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Chairman, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Islamic Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Staff Bulletin, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Chairman, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Visitation Report, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Student Grievance Procedures, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Promotions and Continuing Appointments Procedures, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Promotions and Continuing Appointments Faculty Senate, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Nominations Elections Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Atmospheric Science, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Council on Educational Policy, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Senate Executive Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - College of General Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Vincent Cowling Memoranda, 1971-1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - College of Science and Mathematics Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Science and Mathematics Division Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1976-1977; 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1978; 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Science and Mathematics Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Science and Mathematics Divisions, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Divisions of Science and Mathematics, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Minutes Dept CHRMN DIV. Of Math and Science, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Division of Science and Mathematics, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Seminar for Business and Industry, 1967 October 31-1967 November 3 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Divisional Chairmans Meetings Minutes, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Divisional Chairmans Meetings Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate Studies University College, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate Studies Office of the Dean Robert B. Morris, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Libraries Services Jonathan Ashton, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Common use of Human Subjects, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Univ Review Fall, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Asia Area Studies Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - American Studies Committee, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Area Studies Advisement Committee, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Academic Development Committee, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Academic Development Humanities Committee, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Academic Standing Committee On, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Nominations Committee, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Comm. On Undergrad, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Middle East Area Studies Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - South Asian Area Studies Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Western European Studies Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Honors and Independent Studies Committee On, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - International Exchange of Persons Committee on, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Latin American Area Studies Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Asian Studies Committee, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Asian Study Faculty Committee, 1967-1972 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Central Europe Area Studies Committee (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Colloquium Committee (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Crisis Committee (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Committee (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - East Asia Area Studies Committee (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - East Europe Area Studies Committee (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Conferences Program Committee For (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Review Appeal Panel (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Study and Foreign Students Committee On (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Grading, Committee On (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Political Science Department of (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - General, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Western View Conference (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - SUNYA General College (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - SUNYA Task Force On Instruction (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - International Students (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - SUNYA Minority Group Students (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Social Science Research Unit (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Petersons Guides (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Middle States Association (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Adult Basic Education (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - SUNYA Accreditation and Evaluations (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - University Senate (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - SUNYA University Senate Arts and Sciences Council, 1974 July-1978 June (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Academic Standing of College of Arts and Sciences Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Comm of Academic Standing, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Arts Sciences (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Arts and Sciences Council, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Arts and Sciences Council, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Arts and Science Council Past Years, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Graduate Program in Chemistry Self-Study, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Graduate Program in Chemistry Self-Study, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Deans Office Relocation to SS, 1972 September (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Misc Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Arts Interdisciplinary Majors, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Humanities Administration, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Undergraduate Studies (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Committee on Academic Programs Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Committee On Academic Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Credit Houn (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Committee on Academic Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Academic Standing, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - General, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Community College Seminar, 1967 September 6-1967 September 8 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Dillion Harold, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Leese Joseph, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Teacher Improvement, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Teacher Improvement, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - General, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Heaphey James (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Memoranda to President Collins, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967; 1968; 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Task Force On Academic Regulation Collins, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Task Force On Academic Calendar, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Task Force On Administrative Organization Kuusisto, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Task Force On Experimental Colleges, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Task Force On Instruction, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Task Force On International Education, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Presidents Committee On Interl Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Presidents Committee On Organizations, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Presidents Committee Planning, Budgeting and Information, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Task Forces, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Lewis J, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - SUNYA Foundation, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and General Information, 1966; 1967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1968; 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Interviews by Faculty Members, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mailing Lists, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Printing, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Speakers Bureau Directory, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - SUNYA Senate Elections, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Community Chest Red Cross Joint Appeal, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Contractual Arrangement, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - General, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Agenda, 1966-1967; 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Agenda, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Lecture Center Key, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - General and Agenda, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Standing Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - General Business, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Staff Payroll Information, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Buildings Security, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Student Association, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - General, 1966; 1967 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Statistics on Foreign Students, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Black Eye, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Misc. Dedication Convocation, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Martin L King Vigil, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Peace Corps, SUNYA, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Student Health Service, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - University Counselling Center, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Department of State, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Campus Dedication, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Grants Various, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Religious Studies Committee on, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - List of Committees, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Agenda, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Summaries, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Agenda, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Summaries, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Agenda, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - General, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Agenda, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Agenda, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Summaries, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Agenda, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Summaries, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Thomas Barker, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Brochures, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Brochures, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - OWP's Europe Visit, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Vouchers and Agreements, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Publications Deans Bulletin, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Eugene McLaren, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Department Chairmen, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Pass/Fail Option, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Personnel Data Summary of College Pers., 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Student Participation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Symposium on Violence and Social Change in America, 1968 October 18 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Catalogue College of A & S, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Loads, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Associate Deanships, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Omissions, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Deans Bulletin, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Up-State Conference New Paltz, 1968 October 11 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Academic Revolution, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)